

# Moin Uddin Shourav

# Summary

To find a challenging position to meet my competencies, capabilities, skills, education and experience. I am willing to give total support to the organization with the experience and capability that I have, in order to achieve organization's goals and create mutual benefits.

# Employment History

#### Sr. Executive- CRM & Sales at Gold Sands Limited

Nov, 2020 - Present

- -Plan and carry out all sales activities.
- -Find out sales leads.
- -Team Co-ordination & Reporting.
- -Make a Good Relationship with Client.

## Marketing Specialist at CEMS Global

Dec, 2019 - Nov, 2020

- -Project Manager of: Meditex International Bangladesh, Food and Agro Int'l Expo Bangladesh, Build Bangladesh, Real Estate Int'l Expo.
- -Project Coordinator of: Dhaka Motor Show, Dhaka Bike Show, Dhaka Auto parts Show, Dhaka Commercial Automotive Show, Textech Bangladesh.
- -Special Project country coordinator- QuikAds Bangladesh
- -Maintaining Government and Tender Related Documents and Work.

# Marketing Associate at CEMS Global

Sep, 2018 - Dec, 2019

- -Conduct market research and identify new opportunities.
- -Coordinate with the marketing design and content teams.
- -Assist with organizing promotional events.
- -Monitor and report competitors' marketing and sales activities.

# Jr. Advertising Consultant at Silver Mouse Sdn Bhd

May, 2017 - Dec, 2017

- -Strategic Selling.
- -Networking.
- -Develop and Implement Marketing Strategies.
- -Communicate with Clients.

# Education

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA) at Lincoln University College, Malaysia

CGPA:3.43 out of 4 Major: Marketing

Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC) at BIAM Model High School and College

CGPA:4.70 out of 5 Major: Business Studies

#### **Details**

4/1, Dilu Road, Rajgir Heights, Flat No:C/1, New Eskaton, Ramna, Dhaka

Bangladesh

01704615231

moinshourav@gmail.com

#### Date of birth

07-01-1992

## **Nationality**

Bangladeshi

#### LinkedIn

Moin Shourav

## **Skills**

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Power point)

Marketing & Negotiation

B2B-B2C Sales & Marketing

Market/ Consumer Research

Advertising & Promotion

Digital Marketing (Social Media Marketing)

Photoshop/Illustrator (Basic)

**Event Management** 

# Languages

Bangla

English

# Secondary School Certificate (SSC) at Motijheel Model High School and College

CGPA:4.75 out of 5 Major: Business Studies

# References

Muhammad Awal Khan from Bangladesh Krishi Bank- Former Managing Director

Mobile- 01730338880

Noyeem Sharif from Munshi Bangladesh Limited- Head of Operations

Mobile- 01711081915

## Interests

Watching TVC and Internet browsing.

Reading Articles about Marketing, Branding and Technology